Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/saurabh-liminal (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Film

Marketing

Photography

Languages

Hindi

English

Telugu

Saurabh Ranjan

Founder/Director Liminal Virtual Reality Studio

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

Summary

After the realization set in that I am not going to make it big as a blues drummer (I wasn't close), I started spending my time to practice visual art along with 4 years of engineering which gave me enough prowess to continue my exploration into blending technology with the art of storytelling.

It was late 2014 when I stumbled upon VR and realized the immense potential of this medium to change the way we perceive the world.

After 3 years of creating VR films, ads and immersive experiences I get as excited as I used to, back when I started Liminal VR. Working with leaders to help them think differently and inspire them about the immense value that VR creates for businesses/consumers is what motivates me to continue to be a part of the ever evolving VR industry.

I am also focused on putting my passion and skills to good use by supporting organizations and projects that I really care about. Whether its producing VR documentaries for organizations working on natural disasters, women rights and LGBTQ or using VR for interpersonal transformation.

If you believe that I can help you or you want to know more about VR please get in touch.

https://liminal.in/

My capabilities: VR content, experiential marketing strategy, augmented reality solutions, live VR steaming setup, UI and game design, specialist, process improvement, designing VR workflows, brand and culture.

Experience

Liminal Virtual Reality Studio Founder July 2015 - Present Mumbai Area, India

Housing.com Imagery Researcher January 2015 - November 2015 (11 months) Mumbai Area, India

Education

Jawaharlal Nehru Technological University

B.Tech, Mechanical Engineering; Mechanical Engineering · (2009 - 2013)